export const QUIZZ = [
  {
    description: 'Artists of Velden am Wörter See',
    isLocked: false,
    id: 's1',
    theme: 'Artists of Velden am Wörter See',
    misticStory:
      "STORY-In the very heart of Austria, on the shores of the picturesque lake Velden am Wörthersee, there is an ancient city that hides the secret of a long-forgotten treasure. Legend has it that in ancient times, a local sorcerer cursed the treasure and covered it with an eternal veil of mist so that no one could find it without the right key.  There is a story about a young daredevil named Albert, who decided to solve this mystery and find the treasure. After long research and adventurous search, he came across an ancient map that promised treasure deposits in the depths of the lake. On the night before the full moon, when the fog enveloped the city, Albert set out on a boat to the waters of the lake. Swimming in the direction marked on the map, he suddenly saw a light shining from under the water. Picking up the ancient treasure chest, he heard the voice of the magician: 'You have passed the test and overcome the obstacles, but remember that the treasure carries not only wealth, but also great responsibility.' Returning to the city with the treasure, Albert became the protector of Velden am Wörter See, using the wealth for the good of the residents and the lake. Since that time, the city has flourished, and the legend of the treasure and the brave hero lives on in people's hearts as a symbol of hope and faith in goodness.",
    allQuestions: [
      {
        question: 'Which artist was born in Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: 'Gustav Klimt',
        options: ['Gustav Klimt', 'Egon Schiele', 'Ferdinand Georg Walter'],
      },
      {
        question: 'What style is Gustav Klimt known for?',
        answer: 'Symbolism and modernism',
        options: ['expressionism', 'postmodernism', 'Symbolism and modernism'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Where can you see the works of Gustav Klimt in the city of Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: 'Klimt museums',
        options: [
          'Egon Schiele Museum',
          'Klimt museums',
          'Art Gallery Felden am Werter See',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'What other famous artist also had a connection with the town of Velden am Worthersee? ',
        answer: 'Egon Schiele',
        options: ['Gustav Klimt', 'Egon Schiele', 'Ferdinand Georg Walter'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Where can you see the works of Egon Schiele in the city of Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: 'Egon Schiele Museum',
        options: [
          'Klimt museums',
          'Egon Schiele Museum',
          'Art Gallery Felden am Werter See',
        ],
      },
      {
        question: 'What style is the artist Egon Schiele known for?',
        answer: 'expressionism',
        options: ['Symbolism and modernism', 'expressionism', 'postmodernism'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'His paintings are known for their bright colors and abstract forms. German expressionist artist. The most famous painting is "Blue Horses"',
        answer: 'Franz Mark',
        options: ['Franz Mark', 'Egon Schiele', 'Ferdinand Georg Walter'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'German expressionist artist who also worked in Velden am Werther See. His painting "Street in Berlin" is one of the most famous.',
        answer: 'Ernst Ludwig Kirchner',
        options: [
          'Egon Schiele',
          'Ferdinand Georg Walter',
          'Ernst Ludwig Kirchner',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Austrian artist and graphic artist, known for his mystical and fantastic works. His painting "Dream" is one of the most famous',
        answer: 'Alfred Kubin',
        options: ['Alfred Kubin', 'Egon Schiele', 'Ferdinand Georg Walter'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'What theme prevails in the work of the artist Ferdinand Georg Walter?',
        answer: 'Landscapes and portraits',
        options: ['still life', 'Landscapes and portraits', 'expressionism'],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    description: 'History of Velden am Wörter See',
    isLocked: true,
    id: 's2',
    theme: 'On the history of the city of Velden am Wörter See',
    misticStory:
      "Velden am Wörter See, a picturesque town surrounded by the Alps and located by a magical lake, has always been known for its mystery and legends of ghosts. One of the most famous legends is related to an ancient castle that stood on top of a mountain with a wonderful view of the lake.    The castle once belonged to a powerful family that ruled these lands. However, one dark day, when storm clouds covered the peaks of the Alps, the castle turned out to be shrouded in mystery. Later, rumors were heard that the souls of the deceased relatives of the castle's owners roamed its corridors and towers. One day, a young researcher named Anna decided to investigate this legend. She arrived in Velden am Wörter See to reveal the secret of the castle and to answer the question of the existence of ghosts. Through research and conversations with local residents, she learns of an ancient legend of love, betrayal, and a curse woven into the fate of this place. After many nights spent in the castle, during which Anna listened to the whispering of the wind and strange sounds, she perceived the presence of unseen forces. In the end, she met the ghosts, who told her about their tragic history and how they stayed in their former home until a way to break the curse was found. Through her ingenuity and mental life experience, Anna was able to uncover the true nature of the curse and help the ghosts find peace. Her research became the basis for many books and legends about the castle in Velden am Wörter See and its otherworldly inhabitants. ",
    allQuestions: [
      {
        question: 'In what year was the city of Velden am Wörther See founded?',
        answer: '1313',
        options: ['1150', '1313', '1478'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which river flows through the city of Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Rhine',
        options: ['Rhine', 'Danube', 'Property'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which castle is the symbol of the city of Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Wörtheim Castle',
        options: ['Schweinfurt Castle', 'Würzburg Castle', 'Wörtheim Castle'],
      },
      {
        question: 'Welches Festival ist in Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Beer festival',
        options: [
          'Beer festival',
          'Festival of drawing wine',
          'Music festival',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which dish is traditional for the city of Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Pretzel',
        options: ['Frankfurt sausages', 'Schnitzel', 'Pretzel'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which team represents the city of Velden am Wörther See in football?',
        answer: 'FC Würzburg',
        options: ['FC Würzburg', 'FC Augsburg', 'FC Nuremberg'],
      },
      {
        question: 'Which lake is closest to the city of Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Lake Chiemsee',
        options: ['Lake Constance', 'Lake Chiemsee', 'Lake Constance'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which railway station is the largest inVelden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Hauptbahnhof',
        options: [
          'Hauptbahnhof',
          'Westbahnhof',
          'East Railway Station (Ostbahnhof)',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which architectural monument is the most remarkable in the city of Velden am Wörther See?',
        answer: 'Cathedral',
        options: ['Town Hall', 'Cathedral', 'Maidan Museum'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is the meaning of the name "Velden am Wörther See" in German?',
        answer: 'Field near the Werther River',
        options: [
          'Field near September',
          'Field near the Werther River',
          'Field of vineyards',
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    description: 'Writers of Velden am Wörter See',
    isLocked: true,
    id: 's3',
    theme: 'Famous writers of the city of Velden am Wörter See',
    misticStory:
      "The town of Velden am Wörter See has always been famous for its beauty and tranquility, but behind the deep idyll lay a dark and mysterious history. The legend of the curse began in ancient times, when the city experienced a period of great fever that claimed the lives of many residents. According to legend, one of the local magicians, who was denied treatment for his beloved, decided to take revenge on the city's residents. He uttered a curse that turned on the entire community: 'Until justice is restored and forgiveness is expressed, the city of Velden am Wörter See will be under a curse - darkness and misery will accompany its inhabitants.' Strange events began in the city: people disappeared without a trace, diseases spread faster than usual, and clouds resembling skulls often appeared in the sky. Residents began to panic and look for ways to dilute this curse.   Over the centuries, a number of generations have tried to break the curse, but without success. However, everything changed when a young woman named Anna arrived in town. She was a scientist and magician who decided to accept the challenge and solve the mystery of the curse. Anna researched ancient scrolls and artifacts, performed complex rituals and meditations. Gradually, she realized that the key to solving the curse lay in the forgiveness and mutual understanding of the inhabitants.Through Anna's efforts and the support of the community, the residents began to forgive each other for past grievances and misunderstandings. This act of kindness and simplicity helped lift the curse from the city. Velden am Wörter See came alive with new life: the people became happy and peaceful, and the curse was a thing of the past. Anna remained in the city as a symbol of hope and liberation from the past.",
    allQuestions: [
      {
        question:
          'Which of the Velden am Worthersee writers is known for his philosophical novels and absurd prose, including "The Trial" and "The Castle"?',
        answer: 'Franz Kafka',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Austrian poet and writer from Velden am Worthersee is known for his lyrical and philosophical works such as The Soul and Sonnets to Orpheus?',
        answer: 'Rainer Maria Rilke',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Austrian playwright and novelist from Velden am Werther See became famous for his plays and novels that explore morality?',
        answer: 'Arthur Schnitzler',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Arthur Schnitzler', 'Elfriede Jelinek'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the Austrian writers from Velden am Werther See is the author of the novel "Death in Venice", which became a classic of world literature?',
        answer: 'Herman Brood',
        options: ['Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Herman Brood', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which Austrian writer from Velden am Worthersee won the 2004 Nobel Prize in Literature and is known for her works on social issues and feminist themes?',
        answer: 'Elfriede Jelinek',
        options: ['Elfriede Jelinek', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Herman Brood'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who wrote the novel "The Love Affair" (Die Liebhaberinnen), which takes place in Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: 'Elfriede Jelinek',
        options: [
          'Elfriede Jelinek',
          'Rainer Maria Rilke',
          'Arthur Schnitzler',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which writer wrote the novel "Werther" (Werther), which also takes place in Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: '',
        options: [
          'Franz Kafka',
          'Rainer Maria Rilke',
          'Johann Wolfgang von Goethe',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these writers wrote the tragedy "Electra", which was based on the myths of ancient Greek mythology?',
        answer: 'Herman Brood',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Arthur Schnitzler', 'Herman Brood'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which writer wrote the novel "The Secret of the Heart" (The Secret of the Heart), which is also related to the history of the city of Velden am Worthersee?',
        answer: 'Herman Brood',
        options: ['Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Herman Brood', 'Elfriede Jelinek'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of these writers wrote the poem "Archaischer Torso Apollos" (Archaischer Torso Apollos), which was an inspiration for many artists and writers?',
        answer: 'Rainer Maria Rilke',
        options: [
          'Elfriede Jelinek',
          'Rainer Maria Rilke',
          'Arthur Schnitzler',
        ],
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    description: 'Riddles of Velden am Wörter See',
    isLocked: true,
    id: 's4',
    theme: 'Riddles about the city of Velden am Wörter See',
    misticStory:
      'In the very heart of the city stood a huge ancient building that had once been a luxury hotel for sophisticated travelers. However, over time, the hotel began to become empty, and its walls began to peel off, reminding of its past greatness. Local residents told a legend about the souls of deceased guests who stayed in this hotel, trying to find peace. It was said that at night you can hear whispers and knocks on doors, and sometimes see the faint outlines of ghosts wandering the corridors. One day, a young artist named Liliana arrived in the city to find inspiration for her paintings. She felt attracted by the mysterious hotel and its history, so she decided to stay there for a few weeks. Liliana worked on a series of paintings in which she tried to immortalize the souls of deceased hotel guests. Spending many nights in this place, she felt an extraordinary energy and artistic inspiration that she had not known before. Gradually, Liliana began to perceive the presence of ghosts, which informed her of her tragic fate and desire to find peace. With the help of her artistic creativity, she was able to convey their essence and help them find peace. At the end of her stay at the hotel, Liliana created an unparalleled collection of paintings, which became a kind of memory of the souls of deceased guests. Her works were exhibited at an exhibition in Velden am Wörter See and became an object of admiration for numerous art lovers. ',
    allQuestions: [
      {
        question:
          'He was born in Velden,He created music for the piano.Everyone knows his works Everyone respects him by name. ',
        answer: 'Franz Schubert',
        options: ['Elfriede Jelinek', 'Franz Schubert', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
      {
        question:
          "He created 'Waltzes' and 'Serenades', His melodies flow over the earth.His name lives on in musical hearts,The composer who brought light to all the living.Who is this composer?",
        answer: 'Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart',
        options: [
          'Rainer Maria Rilke',
          'Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart',
          'Elfriede Jelinek',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'He was born in Velden,He wrote his own tragic works.His name in literature sounds,Who is this poet who touched hearts?',
        answer: 'Friedrich Georg',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Arthur Schnitzler', 'Friedrich Georg'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is this world-famous architect? Did he impress the world from Velden am Werther See?Modern buildings and innovations create it,His name in architecture is known throughout the world. Who is he? ',
        answer: 'Zaha Hadid',
        options: ['Franz Kafka', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Zaha Hadid'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Where did he come from, this artist with great talent?Velden am Worthersee is his native home. His paintings are bright, expressive and charming, ',
        answer: 'Egon Schiele',
        options: ['Egon Schiele', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'Who is this great thinker, From Velden am Werther See native, He lives by ethics and morality, He opens his works to the world. ',
        answer: 'Friedrich Nietzsche',
        options: ['Friedrich Nietzsche', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Herman Brood'],
      },
      {
        question:
          'He was born in the city of Velden am Werther See In the cinema he played roles, as a hero he was known. He showed his talents in cult films,Who is this actor who became a star on the screens? ',
        answer: 'Arnold Schwarzenegger',
        options: [
          'Rainer Maria Rilke',
          'Arnold Schwarzenegger',
          'Arthur Schnitzler',
        ],
      },
      {
        question:
          'He was born in the city of Velden-am-Werter-See. The athlete gained fame with his talent. Who is he who rose to the top, He left unsurpassed in his field?',
        answer: 'Franz Clemens',
        options: ['Franz Clemens', 'Rainer Maria Rilke', 'Arthur Schnitzler'],
      },
    ],
  },
];
